leadfeeder.com 2017-08-05

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy policy

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before using the Leadfeeder website located at https://www.leadfeeder.com (the “Website”) or using https://app.leadfeeder.com (the “Service") operated by Liidio Oy ("us", "we", "our" or “Leadfeeder”).

By accessing or using the Website or the Service in any manner you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

### What information does Leadfeeder collect?

#### Visitors of Leadfeeder website, [https://www.leadfeeder.com](https://www.leadfeeder.com/) and Leadfeeder clients using the Leadfeeder service (“Service”)

If you are a visitor to the Website or a Leadfeeder client who registers or signs into the Service via the Website (“Client”), we may obtain the following types of information from you or concerning your computer or device (“Leadfeeder Client Information”), which may include information that can itself be used to identify and/or contact you (“Personally Identifiable Information”):

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Website name and URL
  * Financial information such as credit card or bank account numbers in connection with a transaction
  * Additional information we are required by applicable law to collect

Leadfeeder may also receive certain information that may be provided by your browser or mobile device, including:

  * Pages accessed
  * Time of visit
  * Time of last visit
  * Name of the owner of the IP address
  * Reverse domain of the IP address
  * Referring site, application, or service, including the relevant search queries that led you to Leadfeeder’s website
  * Browser information
  * Operating system information
  * Device information (e.g., device identifier, mobile operating system, etc.)

#### Visitors to Leadfeeder’s Clients’ websites

Leadfeeder obtains information regarding activities of visitors to Clients’ websites (“Client User Data”) through the Google Analytics APIs. When a Client registers to use the Service, the Client authorizes access to the Google Analytics APIs through the Google API web interface. Information relating to Client websites made available to Leadfeeder through the Google Analytics API includes:

  * Pages accessed
  * Time of visit
  * Time of last visit
  * Name of the owner of the IP address
  * Reverse domain of the IP address
  * Referring site, application, or service, including the relevant search queries that led the visitor to Client’s website
  * Browser information
  * Operating system information
  * Device information (e.g., device identifier, mobile operating system, etc.)

#### Information from Leadfeeder’s Clients’ integrations

The Service provides ways to import additional Client User Data from a Client’s other applications and services into the Service. These include for example integrations to customer relationship management (“CRM”) systems and email marketing solutions.

#### Information which may be imported into the Service from CRM systems includes:

  * A Client’s customers, including companies and individuals and related contact information such as name, email, phone number and address.
  * Information about a Client’s activities with its customers, such as phone calls, emails and meetings.

#### Information which may be imported into the Service from email marketing solutions includes:

  * Mailing lists and list subscribers’ email addresses and other additional information.
  * Sent email content.
  * Email receivers’ activities, such as email opens and clicking of links inside the email.

It is the sole responsibility of the Client to ensure that it has obtained permission from its customers and other website users to provide this information to Leadfeeder via the Service. Leadfeeder shall have no liability whatsoever for the failure of any Client to obtain this permission and hereby disclaims such liability. The Client hereby agrees to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Leadfeeder and its affiliates and their respective officers, directors employees, agents, successors and assigns from any third party claims arising from Client’s provision of Client User Data to Leadfeeder using the Service.

The Service may import additional Leadfeeder Client Information from the integrated service, such as settings information.

### What does Leadfeeder use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in any or all of the following ways: * To provide you use of and access to our Website and the Service; * To operate, improve, and personalize our Website and the Service; * To give you access to your account information, provide you with customer service or customer support and to contact you to resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems with your account; * To send periodic emails using the email address you provide to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. * To process payment transactions. * To comply with the law, enforce our Website policies, prevent, detect, and investigate fraud, security breaches, potentially prohibited or illegal activities and to protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. * To enable our trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business, or servicing you, to perform their obligations, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

In addition, we may provide certain Leadfeeder Client Information to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### How Leadfeeder protects your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of Personally Identifiable Information and Client User Data when you enter, submit, or access the information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway provider’s database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and who are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

### How can I access my information?

You can request changes to the Personally Identifiable Information we keep on you by sending a request to support@leadfeeder.com. We will respond to your request upon verification of your identity within a reasonable period of time, and to the maximum extent practical.

Information collected from visitors to Clients’ websites and information imported from Clients’ integrations is available for access to Clients through the Service and through periodic emails the Service sends to Clients.

### Does Leadfeeder use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site and application traffic and interaction so that we can offer better experience and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

Cookies are also used to store current session/login information for the Service.

### Does Leadfeeder disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Client User Data. Leadfeeder Client Information may be transferred to trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release Leadfeeder Client Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. Non-personally identifiable Leadfeeder Client Information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We may also disclose Leadfeeder Client Information, Client User Data and Personally Identifiable Information to allow for a change of ownership of Leadfeeder (including, but not limited to, an acquisition by or merger with another company) and related transfer of all such information to the new owner, in which case any information remains protected in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### How does Leadfeeder respond to Do Not Track Signals?

We may track users over time and across third party websites and we do not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. We do not use this information to provide targeted advertising. Third parties can collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use the Website.

### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our Website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our Website and the Service, but not to information collected offline.

### Links

We may display links to third party websites. Please note that we cannot control and cannot be held responsible for the privacy policies of such websites. You should always read the privacy policy of a website to find out more about how personal information is collected and processed.

We may allow you to share information with third party social media sites, or use social media sites or other sites to create or connect to your account. Those social media sites may give us access to certain personal information stored by them (e.g., content viewed and information about the advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on, etc.) from your interaction with the online services. You control the personal information you allow us to have access to through the privacy settings on that third party website and the permissions you give us when you grant us access. By associating an account managed by a third party with your Leadfeeder account and authorizing us to have access to this information, you agree that we may collect, use and store the information provided by these sites in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Feedback and Posted Information

Certain features of the Website may enable you to submit communications, suggestions, ideas, comments, questions, or other information to us (collectively, “Feedback”) as well as post information to the Website for review by all users of the Website (“Posted Information”). Feedback and Posted Information becomes public information and is submitted at your discretion. When you submit Feedback and Posted Information, you expressly consent to our collection, use and disclosure of such information in any manner.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our Website and the LeadFeeder Service at [https://www.leadfeeder.com](https://www.leadfeeder.com/).

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on January 23, 2017.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below.

Liidio Oy   
Mikonkatu 17 C   
Helsinki 00100   
Finland
